I'm a print designer, so I design prints for fashion, and textiles.
私はプリントデザイナーをやっている。だから、ファッションや、テキスタイルなんかのプリントをデザインするの。
And I'm also a fashion illustrator as well
そしてファッションイラストレーターもやっているわ。
So mine's kind of, there's a big history in textiles so it's kind of old and traditional
だから、私のはなんというか、テキスタイルには大きな歴史があって、それは古くからある伝統的なものなんだけど、
but I'm doing it all digitally.
でも私はそれを全てデジタル的にやっている。
The main things I draw are really feminine. So flowers, girls, um stuff like this
私の描いている主な物は、非常に女性的なの。花とか、女の子とか、そういうもの。
So I'll go out and take a lot of photographs and then I'll do a lot of hand drawings
外に出て沢山の写真を撮って、沢山の絵を描くわ。
and then getting used to that, and then I'll scan them into the computer
そしてそういったことに慣れてきて、それからそれをスキャンしてコンピュータに取り込むの。
and I'll re-draw them on my graphics tablet.
それからそれを再度、タブレットで描き直して、
And it's the digital versions of flowers and stuff, I've colored them all on there as well
デジタルバージョンの花とか、そういうものになる。全てに色も塗るわ。
but they don't look like they've been done on the computer
けれど、それらはコンピュータで全て作りました、という感じにはならず、
they almost look like watercolor.
大体、水彩画のようになるの。
And even when I draw, I'm drawing by hand but onto the screen.。
それから私が手書きをしたとしてもよ。コンピュータスクリーンにだけど。
So it's still, you know it's still me. It's not like me rendering photographs I've taken.
だからそれは、依然として私なのよ。それは撮った写真をレンダリングしているようなものではなくてね。
So I've been going back to hand painting and hand drawing and scanning them in
だから自分の手でペインティングをして、描いて、それをスキャンするところにもどった。
and then printing them out and tearing them up, and usually it's all just screen
そしてそれらをプリントアウトして、破った。普段それは全てただの画面上の事なの。
so I'm loving that at the moment.
だから今のところ、それが好きだわ。
I feel like there's not enough time to put into hand drawing all the creative processes
手で描いた物を全てのクリエイティブなプロセスに通すためには、あまり十分な時間がないと感じてる。
because I work for fashion companies, and they want stuff fast.
なぜなら、ファッション会社の仕事をしていて、彼らは物事を早いペースで求めてくるから。
and so everything has to be done digitally
and so everything has to be done digitally and I do crave
and I do crave just some time to go back to hand drawing.
いつか手書きに戻りたいと切望するのよ。
I've got loads of collaborations at the moment I've got people that want to make jewelry
今のところ、沢山のコラボレーションがあって。宝石を作りたい人たちもいるわ。
out of my stuff, I've got a lead singer of a band that wants to wear all my stuff
私の作品をつかってね。それからバンドのリードボーカルの人もいて、その日とは私の作品を夏のフェスティバルで
to the festivals this summer, it's all about collaboration, really.
身につけたいと言っている。それらは全て、本当にコラボレーションなのよ。
Lots of different companies so lots of different little projects.
沢山の会社と、沢山の小さなプロジェクトをね。